(Nurse:)I got a robot hand grasping
a man's penis out here.
(Howard:)You think you could be
a little more discreet?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry,
we don't have a code for
"robot hand
grasping a man's penis."
(Nurse:)Why is it hooked up
to a computer?
(Leonard:)Uh, it's what
controls the arm.
(Howard:)But it's frozen.
(Nurse:)Did you try turning it off
and back on again?
(Howard:)No, you see, it's more
complicated than that.
(Howard:)No, wait!
(Raj:)Winnie the Pooh
is out of the honey tree.
(Raj:)Now can we have cookies
and Hawaiian Punch?
(Sheldon:)You were right.
(Sheldon:)This was a very
productive evening.
(Sheldon:)I saw a whole new side of
Amy Farrah Fowler tonight.
(Penny:)I did not have
sex with 31 guys.
(Sheldon:)I'll be happy
to check the math,
(Sheldon:)but numbers
don't lie, Penny.